https://worldwish.org/en/website-terms-use-and-cookies-policy

Website Terms of Use and Cookies Policy | Make-A-Wish International
Website Terms of Use and Cookies Policy
View Our Additional PoliciesPrivacy Policy forWish ApplicationsPrivacy Policy for Donors,Sponsors, and VolunteersThank you for visiting Make-A-Wish Foundation® International website https://worldwish.org (the “
Make-A-Wish Website
”).Make-A-Wish Foundation International is one of a number of Make-A-Wish operations around the world which exist exclusively for the charitable purpose of creating life-changing wishes for children with critical illnesses.The Make-A-Wish Website is operated by Make-A-Wish Foundation International of 4742 North 24th Street, Suite 400, Phoenix, Arizona 85016. We are registered with the Arizona Corporation Commission and the Internal Revenue Service as a 501(c)(3) organization with the Employer Identification Number 86-0726985.The following terms and conditions (“Terms”) govern your use of the Make-A-Wish Website and you should read them carefully before using this website. Where we refer to “
Make-A-Wish ”/“we”/“our”/“us” in these Terms, we mean Make-A-Wish Foundation International.To contact us, please email privacy@worldwish.org.WHAT THESE TERMS COVERThese Terms include:Our “Terms of Use”, which govern the use of the Make-A-Wish Website;Our “Cookie Policy”, which sets out information about the cookies on the Make-A-Wish Website.These Terms also refer to (a) our “Privacy Policy for Wish Applications”; and (b) our “Privacy Policy for Donors, Sponsors, and Volunteers”, which set out the terms on which we process personal information we collect from certain individuals, or that is provided to us.We may amend these Terms from time to time. Please check these Terms regularly to ensure you understand the terms that apply at that time.WEBSITE TERMS OF USEACCESSING THE MAKE-A-WISH WEBSITEBy accessing and using the Make-A-Wish Website, you confirm that you accept these Terms of Use and that you agree to comply with them.If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, you must not use the Make-A-Wish Website.WE MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THE MAKE-A-WISH WEBSITEWe may update and change the Make-A-Wish Website from time to time to reflect changes to, for example, our users’ needs or technical, operational or other business priorities.WE MAY SUSPEND OR WITHDRAW THE MAKE-A-WISH  WEBSITEWe do not guarantee that the Make-A-Wish Website, or any content on it, will always be available or be uninterrupted. We may suspend or withdraw or restrict the availability of all or any part of the Make-A-Wish Website for technical, operational and/or business reasons. We will try to give you reasonable notice of any suspension or withdrawal.We will not be liable to you if, for any reason, the Make-A-Wish Website is unavailable at any time.HOW YOU MAY USE MATERIAL ON THE MAKE-A-WISH WEBSITEWe are the owner or the licensee of any and all intellectual property rights in the Make-A-Wish Website and in the material published on it. Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world. All such rights are reserved.You may print off one copy, and may download extracts, of any page(s) from the Make-A-Wish Website for your personal use.You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text.Our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of content on the Make-A-Wish Website must always be acknowledged.You must not use any part of the content or materials on the Make-A-Wish Website for commercial purposes without obtaining a license to do so from us or our licensors.If you print off, copy or download any part of the Make-A-Wish Website in breach of these Terms of Use, your right to use the Make-A-Wish Website will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made.DO NOT RELY ON THE INFORMATION ON THE MAKE-A-WISH WEBSITEThe content which we provide on the Make-A-Wish Website (including any content in our social media posts) is provided for general information only. It is not intended to amount to advice on which you should rely.Although we make reasonable efforts to update the information on the Make-A-Wish Website, we make no representations, warranties or guarantees, whether express or implied, that the content on the Make-A-Wish Website is accurate, complete or up to date.WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR WEBSITES WE LINK TOWhere the Make-A-Wish Website contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources.WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR VIRUSES AND YOU MUST NOT INTRODUCE THEMWe do not guarantee that the Make-A-Wish Website will be secure or free from bugs or viruses. You should use your own virus protection software.You must not misuse the Make-A-Wish Website by knowingly introducing viruses, trojans, worms, logic bombs or other material that is malicious or technologically harmful. You must not attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Make-A-Wish Website, the server on which the Make-A-Wish Website is stored or any server, computer or database connected to the Make-A-Wish Website. You must not attack the Make-A-Wish Website via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of service attack. By breaching this section, you may be committing a criminal offence. We will report any such breach to the relevant law enforcement authorities and we will co-operate with those authorities by disclosing your identity to them. In the event of such a breach, your right to use the Make-A-Wish Website will cease immediately.To the fullest extent permissible by law, we will not be liable to you for any loss or damage caused by a distributed denial-of-services attack, viruses, or other technologically harmful material that may infect your computer equipment, computer programs, data or other proprietary material due to your use of the Make-A-Wish Website or to your downloading of any material posted on it, or any website linked to it.HOW WE MAY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe will only use your personal information as set out in:(a) our Privacy Policy for Wish Applications; and/or(b) our Privacy Policy for Donors, Sponsors and Volunteers.RULES ABOUT LINKING TO THE Make-A-Wish WEBSITEYou may link to our home page or sign-in page, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it.You must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval or endorsement on our part where none exists.You must not establish a link to the Make-A-Wish Website in any website that is not owned by you.The Make-A-Wish Website must not be framed on any other website, nor may you create a link to any part of our site other than the home page.We reserve the right to withdraw linking permission without notice.If you wish to link to or make any use of content on the Make-A-Wish Website other than that set out above, please contact us at privacy@worldwish.org. LAWS APPLYING TO ANY DISPUTESThese Terms of Use, their subject matter and their formation, are governed by State of Arizona. You and we both agree that the Superior Court of the State of Arizona in and for the County of Maricopa and the United States District Court for Arizona will have exclusive jurisdiction except that if you are a resident in another jurisdiction, you may also bring proceedings in your home jurisdiction.In addition, please note that disputes may be submitted for online resolution to the European Commission Online Dispute Resolution platform: https://webgate.ec.europa.eu/odr/main/index.cfm?event=main.home.chooseLanguage]SEVERABILITYIf any court or competent authority decides that any of the provisions of these Terms of Use are invalid, unlawful or unenforceable to any extent, the provision will, to that extent only, be severed from the remaining provision, which will continue to be valid to the fullest extent permitted by law.MISCELLANEOUSAny words following the terms including, include, in particularfor example or any similar expression shall be construed as illustrative and shall not limit the sense of the words, description, definition, phrase or term preceding those terms.COOKIE POLICYWe use cookies, which are small files of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer or other electronic device if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to the hard drive of your computer or electronic device.We use the following cookies:Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies which are required for the operation of the Make-A-Wish Website. [They include, for example, cookies that enable the Make-A-Wish Website to ‘remember’ the amount that someone has chosen to donate when they click the ‘donate’, ‘proceed’ or ‘next’ button.]Analytical/performance cookies. These are cookies which allow us to recognise and count visitors and to see how visitors move around the Make-A-Wish Website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way the Make-A-Wish Website works.Functionality cookies. These are cookies which are used to recognise you when you return to the Make-A-Wish Website. This enables us to personalise content for you and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).Targeting/advertising cookies. These are cookies which record your visit to the Make-A-Wish Website, the parts of the Make-A-Wish Website you have visited and any links you have followed. We may use this information to make the Make-A-Wish Website more relevant to your interests or to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.The information might be used for frequency capping purposes and to help us regulate the advertisements you receive and measure their effectiveness.By continuing to access and use the Make-A-Wish Website you accept our use of these cookies.You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of some or all cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or part of our site and/or it might not work as you expect it to.For more detailed information about cookies and how they can be managed and deleted, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.WE MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THIS COOKIE POLICYWe may amend this Cookie Policy from time to time. Please check this Cookie Policy regularly to ensure you understand the terms that apply at that time. This Cookie Policy was most recently updated in May 2018.
Site Map
About UsMake-A-Wish® Story
Board of Directors
International Office
Financials
Press Releases
Media Kit and Contacts
Careers and Internships
1702 E Highland Ave,
©2019-2020 Make-A-Wish Foundation® International  |  Designed by Hinduja Tech
